# Nofrialdi

# Full Stack Engineer



aldi.fasive@gmail.com



0896-1202-2458





Github

Bachelor of Informatics Systems with interest in programming. Have an understanding of application and web development, as well as database management. Skilled in Java and PHP programming languages and familiar with HTML, CSS, Javascript, TypeScript, React.js framework, Next.js codeigniter and postgresql, mySql. I have experience as an assistant programming instructor and have also been an Android developer. With the experience and understanding I have, I hope to become a full stack engineer in the future.

# **Experience**

# CV. Bina Kreasi Informatika

Jan, 2018 - Nov, 2019

# Programming assistant instructor

- Assist training at TNI Headquarters in the field of programming, especially website and Android training, through a structured curriculum.
- installed 40 computers that did not have the required applications before the training began, such as XAMPP, Android Studio, and Visual Studio Code.
- Training 40 TNI Headquarters students how to create websites from basic HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to using the CodeIgniter framework
- I trained 40 students at TNI Headquarters on how to make Android applications using the Android Studio application using Java and XML.

#### PT. Fedora

Sep, 2016 - Dec, 2017

# Android developer

- Create UI/UX designs for Android applications for clients using the Figma application.
- Implement the UI/UX design into the application using Android Studio using the Java and XML programming languages.
- Connect the application with the database that has been provided by the team.
- Carry out maintenance on the applications created, starting with bug fixes and application optimization.

# STMIK Jayakarta

Aug, 2015 - Jul, 2016

#### Assistant lecturer

- Help the lecturer teach in the classroom and deliver material to the students.
- Help fill in lecture activities and replace the lecturer leading the class if the lecturer is unable to attend.
- Create questions and answers for students; help compile course syllabi.

#### **Education**

Revou Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

#### **Full Stack Software Engineering**

• At Revou, I learned how to create a website, from the basics of HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Typescript to creating a website using the React JS and Next JS frameworks. Apart from that, I also learned how to create a UI/UX and a backend using Nest JS.

# STMIK Jayakarta

Sep 2013 - April 2017

### **Bachelor of Computer Science**

• I graduated from STMIK Jayakarta with the title "Human Respiratory System Application Design for Android-Based Primary Schools. I graduated with a GPA of 3.5.

#### **Skills**

#### **Technical Skill**

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, Xml, Javascript, Bootstrap, Tailwiness
- Framework: React.js, Next.js, Codeigniter
- Database: MySql, Postgresql
- Backend: Php, Nestjs, Java
- Service architecktures: RestAPI
- DevOps: Docker, Gcp (Google Cloud Platform)

#### Soft Skill

- Collaboration and Teamwork
- Time Management
- Problem-Solving Skills
- Communication

# **Project**

#### • Web Portofolio

- Techstack: Html, Css, React.js, Javascrpict, Tailwiness
- Link Repository: https://github.com/nofrialdi/nofri-portofilio
- Link Website: https://nofri-portofilio.vercel.app/

# Web Markilang

- Techstack: Html, Css, Next.js, Typescript, Tailwincss
- Link Repository: https://github.com/revou-fsse-1/w24-group-final-group-2
- Link Website: https://markilang.vercel.app/